Kashkan Sergey

Junior QA Engineer

I'm a junior qa engineer, have higher education in computer engineering. I have basic skills in functional testing. Also i have little experience in webprogramming. I am a good team player, but i can work independently too. Ready to work and develop my skills

Contact information

- in SergeyKashkan
- sega8800

Phone number

+375 (29) 195-50-77

Experience

Sep. 2018 - Jun. 2023

Student BSUIR

- Writing documentation, such as check lists, acceptance sheets, test cases and bug reports.
- Conducted testing of training projects, such as documentation and webapplications.
- Formalization bugs and errors in bug reports.

Jun. 2022 - Jul. 2022

Practice Art-Term

- Organisation site administration in Axiom CRM.
- Site optimisation.

Oct. 2019 - Dec. 2019

QA Student IT-Academy

- Creating requirements to web-site it-academy.by.
- Write test documentation, such as check lists, test cases and test plan.
- Testing documentation.
- Testing web-site.
- Writing bug-reports and make testing report.

Skills

Functional testing - Manual testing - Writing test documentation - JavaScript - HTML - CSS - React -Github - Redux - Node.JS - Figma

Education

Sep. 2018 - Jun. 2023

Engineering-Psychological Maintenance of Information Technologies

Belarusian State University of Information and Radioelectronics

Oct. 2019 - Dec. 2019

Functional Testing

IT-Academy

Language

Russian (Native) Belorussian (Native) English (A2-B1)